medtechy.com 2019-12-26

# Medtechy: The Place for Biotechnology & Medical Device News | Medtechy

We use Ezoic to provide personalization and analytic services on this website, as such Ezoic's privacy policy is in effect and can be reviewed [here](https://g.ezoic.net/privacy/medtechy.com).  

Medtechy LLC ("Company," "we," "us," or "our") created this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") to explain how we use personal information, as defined below, and to give you assurance of our commitment to fair information practices and to the protection of your privacy as you visit and use the Medtechy.com website (the "Website").

We understand that you value your privacy and the right to control how your personal information is collected and used. Our data collection and retention practices are designed to provide transparency, accountability and choice regarding the management and use of your personal information.

We also provide you with contact information should you wish to remove your personal information from our databases.

This Privacy Policy shall be interpreted under the laws of the United States. Whether or not required to register on the Website, you explicitly accept, without limitation or qualification, the collection, use, and transfer of your information in the manner described in this Privacy Policy. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully as it affects your rights and liabilities under the law. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and part of, the [ **Website Terms of Use**](https://www.medtechy.com/terms-of-use) which govern your use of the Website, in general.

If you do not agree to our practices, please do not interact in any manner whatsoever with the Website or register any personally identifiable information on this Website. Please contact us if you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy. You can reach us via postal mail at Medtechy LLC, 400 S. 4th Street, Suite 500, Las Vegas, Nevada 89101.

**THIS WEBSITE IS NOT INTENDED FOR ANYONE UNDER THE AGE OF EIGHTEEN (18). BY USING THE WEBSITE, YOU EXPRSSLY REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOU HAVE READ, UNDERSTOOD AND AGREE TO THE TERMS OF THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF YOU DO NOT UNDERSTAND OR DO NOT AGREE TO BE BOUND BY THIS PRIVACY POLICY AND OUR WEBSITE TERMS OF USE, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY LEAVE THE WEBSITE.**

**1\. Types of Information We Collect**

Personally identifiable information is information that can be used to identify, locate, or contact an individual. When a job-seeker or a recruiter fills out a registration form on the Website, we may collect such information as first name, last name and email address (collectively referred to herein as "PII"). In conjunction with the submission of a resume, Company recommends that you do not include sensitive PII, including, without limitation, credit card number, banking information, social security number and/or driver’s license number.

We also reserve the right to collect certain non-personally identifiable information ("NPII") about any/all visitors, whether a user or non-user, when they visit many of the pages of this Website. This NPII includes, without limitation, the type of browser or device used, the Internet Protocol ("IP") address, the type of operating system used and/or the domain name of the Internet service provider. An IP address is a unique identifier that a device uses to identify and communicate with on the Internet.

 **2\. How Your Information is Used and Shared by Company**

We value your privacy and have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with relevant legislation, including, without limitation, the California Online Privacy Protection Act.

We ask you for PII when you register on the Website as a job-seeker or a recruiter. WITH THE EXCEPTION OF THOSE POSTING POTENTIAL EMPLOYMENT OPPORTUNITIES AND CANDIDTATE APPLICANTS, MEDTECH[Y] PERMITS USERS TO UTILIZE THE WEBSITE ANONYMOUSLY AND DOES NOT STORE ANY PII.

By providing PII, you expressly authorize us to disclose or share your information in order to provide the services offered via the Website, including, without limitation, transmission of PII to a potential employer. You also assent to receive, from time to time, email correspondence for the purposes of solicitation from Company. You can unsubscribe anytime by following the opt-out instructions included in the relevant communication or by contacting us directly via email at [info@medtechy.com](mailto:info@medtechy.com) or in writing to 400 S. 4th St., #500, Las Vegas, NV 89101.

If you are located in Canada, Company may be required to obtain your prior express consent to receive commercial electronic messages in order for us to comply with Canadian Anti-Spam Legislation. If you do not provide your express opt-in to receive emails and you reside in Canada, you may not receive emails from us. As a result, you hereby release Company from any responsibility if you fail to receive information that you would have otherwise received.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request and obtain from Company a list of what PII we disclosed to third-parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year, as well as the names and addresses of those third parties. Requests may be made only once a year and are free of charge. Company does not share, sell or transfer your PII to third-parties for direct marketing purposes.

**YOU MAY OPT-OUT OF RECEIVING MOST COMMUNICATIONS FROM US BY CHOOSING NOT TO SUBMIT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION. IF YOU HAVE ALREADY SUBMITTED YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO US AND WISH TO OPT-OUT AND/OR DELETE YOUR ACCOUNT AT A LATER DATE, YOU MAY DO SO BY SENDING US A REQUEST  [HERE](mailto:info@medtechy.com).**

Company also reserves the right to use technology information to match your PII to make and improve profiles of you, to track your online browsing habits over time and across different websites on the Internet, to show you targeted advertising for products and/or services and/or to determine which areas of the Internet are most frequently visited. As such, Company reserves the right to target advertising to you by using email, targeted online banner advertising, applications and other means of communication to provide promotional offers. Company may also use your PII for data verification purposes, to resolve disputes, troubleshoot technical problems, enforce our agreements with you and to enable Company to personalize your Internet experience.

Company may share your PII with third-parties who help us in the delivery the services you have requested and to companies/individuals we employ to perform technical functions on our behalf. These companies and individuals may not share that information with any other third-party or use that data for any other purpose.

By visiting and/or supplying your PII at this Website, you also agree to allow us to provide aggregated anonymous data about you to third-parties so that they can understand the kinds of visitors to the Website and in order to offer you products and services. This includes demographic information and behavioral information. 

Company may disclose PII, as permitted by law. We may disclose and transfer any/all information to a third-party who acquires any or all of our business, whether such acquisition is by way of merger, consolidation or purchase of all or a substantial portion of our assets. In addition, in the event we become the subject of an insolvency proceeding, whether voluntary or involuntary, we or our liquidator, administrator, receiver or administrative receiver may sell, license or otherwise dispose of such information in a transaction approved by the court.

**3\. Company and Third-Party Cookies, Web Beacons, Pixel Tags, Log Files and Online Behavioral Technologies**

The Website and email messages may contain first-party (Company-related) cookies, web beacons, pixel tags, browser analysis tools and web server logs that enable Company to track your online behavior, collect information regarding your operating system and browser/device type, record what webpage or email you viewed, track the IP address of the device you use to interact with the applicable online service, record when you open or click on a particular online advertisement link or webpage, and additionally for other information gathering purposes such as the language your system uses and the country and time zone of your device. 

A cookie is a small file uniquely assigned to you by a webpage server when you visit a webpage or click on a link and can assist in associating your information to a unique profile. Cookies are stored in web server logs and also in web cookies kept on your computer, which are then transmitted back to us by your computer. They store information about your account, preferences, your use of the Website and your online browsing habits. They allow us to recognize you when you return, and track and target your interests in order to provide a customized experience. They also assist with the provision of a customized browsing experience and with the detection of certain kinds of fraud. 

Some cookies are temporary, whereas others may be configured to last longer. "Session" cookies are temporary cookies used for various reasons, such as to manage page views. Your browser usually erases session cookies once you exit your browser. "Persistent" cookies are more permanent cookies that are stored on your computer even beyond when you exit your browser. Your browser preferences may be able to be modified to accept or reject all cookies, or request a notification when a cookie is set. However, because an industry-standard Do-Not-Track protocol has not yet been established,  **Company's information collection practices will continue to operate as described in this Privacy Policy regardless of any "Do Not Track" signals that may be sent by certain browsers or selected by you.**

If you wish to opt-out of receiving most communications from Company, you can follow the opt-out instructions in the respective communications that are sent to you. You may read more about cookies at [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/) and aboutads.info. 

Pixel tags and web beacons are tiny graphic images placed on website pages or in emails that allow Company to determine whether you have performed specific actions. When you access these pages or open email messages, the pixel tags and web beacons generate a notice of that action. These tools permit the measurement of responses to communications and improve related promotions. You may read more about web beacons at webopedia.com. 

Log files include IP addresses, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer a website, track user's movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. 

As set forth herein, Company collects many different types of information from cookies and other technologies, including, without limitation, what website you were visiting before you came to the Website, the website you visit after you leave the Website, and other activities or yours over time and across third-party websites and online services.

**4\. Security of Your Personally Identifiable Information**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information we gather online, Company stores your PII in a database on secure systems. We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and managerial security procedures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Access to this information is strictly limited, and not accessible to the public. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to PII. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all user information, to the extent reasonably possible. Employees who do not adhere to our firm policies are subject to disciplinary action. Notwithstanding such measures, Company cannot guarantee that its security measures will prevent Company computers from being illegally accessed, and the data on them stolen or altered, and Company assumes no responsibility for such actions. You may request that your information be modified or deleted, as detailed herein. In compliance with applicable federal and state laws, we shall notify you and any applicable regulatory agencies in the event that we learn of an information security breach with respect to your PII.

**5\. No Information Collected from Children**

Company encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children. Company will never knowingly collect any Personal Information about children under the age of thirteen (13). If Company obtains actual knowledge that it has collected Personal Information about a child under the age of thirteen (13), that information will be immediately deleted from its database. Because we do not collect such information, Company has no such information to use or to disclose to third-parties. Company has designed this policy in order to comply with the Children's Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA").

**6\. Links to Other Websites and Third-Party Privacy Practices**

Company may provide links to other websites for your convenience and information. These websites may have their own privacy statements in place. We are not responsible for the content of linked websites or any use of such websites. Whether linked or not, you expressly acknowledge that other websites have their own privacy statements and personal information collection, use, and disclosure practices. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy statements provided by any/all third-party websites prior to providing them with information or taking advantage of an offer or promotion.

**7\. Changes to This Privacy Policy**

Company reserves the right to change or remove portions of our Privacy Policy at any time without prior notification. If Company changes this Privacy Policy updates will be posted herein. Information will be used in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. Please check the Website frequently to apprise yourself of any changes that may affect you. The posting of any changes will be the only notice that you will receive regarding any such amendments or changes.

**8\. Privacy Inquiries or Complaints**

Company strives to keep all PII accurate and complete. You are always fully in control of the information that we maintain to service you. You can also request that PII be deleted, however, Company reserves the right to retain information in our archives and/or as necessary to establish lawful marketing consent.

If you have any inquiries regarding our privacy practices, believe that we have not complied with this Privacy Policy, notice a suspicious job posting, believe you have been the victim of fraud or would like to access and modify your PII, please contact us via email at [info@medtechy.com](mailto:info@medtechy.com). You may also write to us, here:

Medtechy LLC400 S. 4th Street, Suite 500Las Vegas, Nevada 89101

**9\. Privacy Inquiries or Complaints**

In accordance with California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to [dca@dca.ca.gov](mailto:dca@dca.ca.gov). For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: [http://www.ftc.gov](http://www.ftc.gov/). If you have questions about this policy, please contact us at info@medtechy.com.
